A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art AAA.neimlero
Archives of American Art
Halle, David - 3.1: UCLA LeRoy Neiman Center for the Study of American Society and Culture, 1998-present; A Sociological Study of the Artist LeRoy Neiman, and 1000 Neiman Collectors by David Halle and Louis Mirrer - IC: A Sociological Study of the Artist LeRoy Neiman, and 1000 Neiman Collectors by David Halle and Louis Mirrer, 1990
Halmi, Robert - 3.2.12 and 4.1: undated ov
Hammer Galleries - see exhibitions, and Knoedler & Co.
Hammer, Armand - 1.2: Knoedler & Co. and Hammer Galleries, 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001, 3.1: Tretyakov Museum Solo Exhibition, Moscow 1988, 3.1: Tokyo exhibition 1988
Hammer, Michael - 1.2: Knoedler & Co. and Hammer Galleries
Hammer, Victor - 1.2: Knoedler & Co. and Hammer Galleries
Hammond, IN - see Mercantile Bank
Hampton, Kym - 4.1: 2000
The Hamptons, New York - 3.1: Hamptons notes 1972, 4.2: Playboy 1973, see Appendix E handball - see Jacobs, Jim
Hanson Gallery, New Orleans - see exhibitions, 3.1: Rex Proclamation Mardi Gras Painting 2002, 4.1: 1984, 1986, 1998, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2004
Hanson Gallery, San Diego - 4.1: 1987
Harbor Boat House, 1955 - 4.1: 1950s
Hardy, Joseph A. - 1.1: Collectors
Harlem Streets, 1981 - 3.1: Cities in Schools and Harlem Streets, 1981
harlequin
Harlequin, lithograph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1989
Harlequin and a Nude, 1971 - 4.1: 1991
Harlequin with Sword, lithograph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Harlequin's Entry into Venice, 1971 mural - 3.1: "The Playboy Collection," Dyansen Gallery Traveling Exhibition 1989-90
Haring, Keith - 4.1: 1997
Harmon Galleries - see Foster Harmon Galleries
Harper's Magazine - 4.1: 1964, 1968
Harrod's, London - 4.1: 1982
Harry, Deborah - 2.1: 1978
Harry's Wall Street Bar - see bars
Hartack, Bill - 2.1: 1977
Harvard University - 4.2: Playboy Parodies - Harvard and Yale
Haskell, Nikki - 4.1: 1980, 1981, 1982, 1984, 1985, 1987, 1990, 2002, 2004
Nikki, 1984 (in Carnaval garb) - 4.1: 1985, 1987
Nikki Haskell, 2000 - 4.1: 2000
Nikki Haskell, 2002 - 2.1: 2002, 4.1: 2002
hats - VII
Hawaii - 4.1: 1980 ov
Hayes, Isaac - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004
Healey, Kathy - see figure skating
Hearns, Thomas - see boxing
Heartland Celebrity Cookbook - 4.1: 1991
Heath Gallery, Atlanta, GA - 4.1: 1969
The Heavyweights, vinyl LP recording 1970 - see boxing
Heavyweight Explosion, 2000 - see boxing
Hebner, Richie
Richie Hebner - 4.1: 1973
Hefner, Christie - 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1980s, 3.1: Playboy's LeRoy Neiman Selection Cigars 1997
Hefner, Hugh - 1.1: Education and Teaching b., 1.1: Friars ov., 2.1: 1996, 1999, 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1980s, 3.1: Playboy Scrapbook 1961-67, 4.1: 1985, V: Playboy 1961-63, see also Playboy Magazine
Heiden, Eric - 3.1: Winter Olympics, Lake Placid 1980
Heit Galleries - 2.1: 1987, 1988, see also exhibitions
helicopter - 3.1: WNBC Traffic Helicopter 1981-1995
Hello, I Must Be Going: Groucho & his Friends - see Chandler, Charlotte
Helsinki, Finland - see exhibitions
"Here's Looking at You, Kid," 1990 - see Wine Country Film Festival
Hernandez, Genaro - 4.1: 1995
Hernquist, Lee - 4.1: 2002
Herrick, Norton - 4.1: 1998
Hershiser, Orel - 2.1: 1992
Heyden, Eric - see Knoedler
High Ball Homer, 1962 - see Mantle, Mickey
High Seas Sailing - see sailing
High Seas Sailing II, 1998 - see sailing
high society - see socialites
Hill, Calvin - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-1973, 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams, Correspondence, 4.1: 1973, Calvin Hill - 4.1: 1979
Hilliard Gallery - 2.1: 1975, 1977, 1978, 1989, 4.1: 1986, 1992, 2001, see exhibitions
Hilliard, Chet - 4.1: 1995
Hilliard, Kent - 4.1: 1990, see Hilliard Gallery
Hilton Hotels - 2.1: 1991
Hinds, Bobby - see boxing
Hines, Jerome and Lucia - see opera
Hispanic Sports Awards Dinner - 2.1: 1991
"History of Sport in Art" film series - 2.1: 1972
HOBY - 4.1: 1997
hockey - search for individual players by name, see also Olympic Games
Choate Prep School hockey - 4.1: 1970
The French Connection, 1976 - 4.1: 1978
Hockey etchings - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Hockey Magazine - 2.1: 1977
NHL hockey - 3.1: Wayne Gretzky portraits 1981-2002, 4.1: 1967
Boston Bruins - see Orr, Bobby
Heisman Trophy - 2.1: 1982
Houston Aeros - 4.1: 1975
NHL Challenge Cup (USA All -Stars vs. USSR National) - 4.1: 1979
New Jersey Devils - 4.1: 1998
New York Rangers - 4.1: 1966, 1967, 1976, 1998, 1999, 2000
Phoenix Coyotes - 3.1: Wayne Gretzky 2002
Ottawa Senators - 3.1: Wayne Gretzky 2002
Stanley Cup - 4.1: 1974
Hoelscher, Lydia (LeRoy's mother) - 1.1: Family (Neiman Studio Archive only)
Hofstra University - 1.1: Honorary Degrees, 3.1: Hofstra Univ. Frank Sinatra Conference and Exhibition 1998, 4.1: 1996
Hogan, Hulk - see wrestling
Hoglund, William - 2.1: 1983
Holder, Geoffrey - 4.1: 1978
holiday, Christmas - 4.1: 1992, 1995, 1997
Hollywood Women's Press Club - see Golden Apple Awards
Holmes, Larry - see boxing
Holyfield, Evander - see boxing
Holzman, Red - 4.1: 1990
Homage to Boucher - 4.1: 1974
Homansky, Dr. Flip - 3.1: Ringside and Training Principles by Goodman and Homansky 2001
Home Remodeling Magazine - 4.1: 1965
Home Run Blast, 2002 etching - see baseball
honorary degrees - 1.1: Honorary degrees
Hope, Bob - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993, 4.1: 1984, Bob Hope (Playing Golf), 1988 - 3.1: Bob Hope portrait, 1988
Hope House Ministries - 4.1: 1995, 1996
Horizon Gallery - 4.1: 1980
Horse of a Different Color, Ltd. - 4.1: 1963
horses - see also polo, rodeo, sculpture
Arabians - 4.1: 1978
Arabians Magazine - 4.1: 1982, 1984, 1985, 1986
Bucking Bronco - 4.1: 1984
Carousel, 195? - 2.1: 1975, 4.1: 1950s
Color Horse - 4.1: 1984
Clydesdales - see promotions
Daily Double - 4.1: 1982, 1984
French Hunt, 1965 - V: Early 1960s Photos of Work
Horses, 1979 - 3.2.3
Ladies of the Hunt, 1959 charcoal drawing - 2.1: 1973, 3.1: Knoedler London Exhibition 1976, 4.1: 1950s
horse racing - 4.1: 1997
Aintree - 4.1: 1960
Ascot - see Royal Ascot
Belmont Park - 4.1: 1980, 2003
The Paddock at Belmont - 4.1: 1979
Bellocq, Pierre - 4.1: 1998
The Black Stallion - see television
Breeders' Cup - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 2003
Breeders' Cup Championship poster, 1998 - 3.1: Breeders' Cup Painting 1998
Caliente Race Track, Tijuana, Mexico - 3.1: Caliente Race Track Exhib. and Painting 1989, 4.1: 1991
Chantilly, Backstretch at Chantilly - 4.1: 1969
The Charging Cavalcade, silkscreen - 4.1: 1980
Charismatic - 4.1: 1999
Churchill Downs - 3.1: 123rd Kentucky Derby 1997, 4.1: 1996, VII: Box 3
Club House Turn, 1975 serigraph - 1.2: Knoedler Serigraph Release Ads, 4.1: 1975, undated 1990s, 1989
Curragh, Ireland, 1976 drawing - 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95
Epsom Derby - 4.1: 1960, 4.2: Playboy 1964, see Appendix E
Equestrianne - 4.1: 1981, 2000
Equestrian, 1974 watercolor - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975-76
The Feria in Seville - 4.1: 1982, 1984, 1985
The Finish - 4.1: undated
Florida Derby - 2.1: 1992, 4.1: 1993
Four Acres, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1973
Front Runners, 1994 - 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95
Funnycide - 4.1: 2003
Grand National Steeplechase, Liverpool - 4.1: 1960 and ov, 4.2: Playboy 1962, see Appendix E
Grand Prairie, Lone Star Park - 3.1: National All-Star Jockey Championships 2001
Hambletonian - 3.1: Cadillac Hambletonian Harness Race Painting 1995
Hialeah Race Track - 2.1: 1977, 3.1: Hialeah Race Track, 1959, 4.2: Playboy 1959, see Appendix E
Hong Kong Jockey Club - 4.1: 2004
Hoof Beats Magazine - 4.1: 1975
horse named after LeRoy Neiman - 2.1: 1987
Horse Racing, 1972 watercolor - 4.1: 1998
Horse Racing Suite, 1977 - see sculpture
Horse and Rider, 1971 gouache - 2.1: 1974
Horse Sense: An Inside Look at the Sport of Kings, by Bert Sugar, cover illustration by LeRoy Neiman - 2.1: 2002, 4.1: 2002
In the Stretch, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
International Horse Show - 4.1: 1973
Iroquois Steeplechase, 1993 - 3.1: Iroquois Steeplechase, Nashville, TN, 1993
jockeys - jockeys - see also horse racing, 3.1: "Dress the Jockeys", '21' Club 2001
The Backview of Jockey, 1961 - 4.1: Four Jockeys - 4.1: undated
Hartack, Bill, Bill Hartack, 1959 - 3.1: Hialeah Race Track 1959, 4.1: 1974, 1995
Jockey, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Jockey - 4.1: 1961
Krone, Julie - 2.1: 2003
Solomon, Mickey - 2.1: 1989
Kelso, 1968 drawing - 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95
Kentucky Derby - 2.1: 1982, 3.1: 123rd Kentucky Derby 1997, 4.1: 1978, VII: Box 3
Derby Day Paddock, 1997 - 3.1: 123rd Kentucky Derby 1997
Kentucky Derby Museum - 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95
Long Island Equestrienne - 4.1: 1982, 1984
Longchamps - 4.1: 1960
Menlo Charity Horse Show - 4.1: 2003
Mission Valley Pony Club - 4.1: 1990
Monmouth Park - 4.1: 1969
Monmouth Park Centennial, 1970 - 4.1: 1970, 1971, 1975
National All -Star Jockey Championships - 3.1: National All-Star Jockey Championships 2001
National Horse Show - 4.2: Playboy 1967, see Appendix E
National Showcase, Louisville, KY - 4.1: 1982
New York Racing Association (NYRA) - 2.1: 1978
Paddock, 1957 painting - 2.2: JoAnn Perse Gallery 1984-98
Paddock, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95 4.1: 1973
Pegasus, 1979 - New Jersey State Opera Ball Paintings 1979-83
polo horses - see polo
Pimlico - 3.1: 125th Preakness Stakes 2000, VII: Box 3
Preakness Stakes - 3.1: 125th Preakness Stakes 2000
The Race, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, V: 1970s
Race of the Year, 1979 - 3.1: Race of the Year 1979
Racing, 1972 - 4.1: 1972
The Reinsman - 4.1: 1963
The Rider, pre-1966 - 4.1: 1966
Rotz with Windener Coulours, pre-1966 - 4.1: 1966
Royal Ascot - 4.1: 1960, 1961, 4.2: Playboy 1966, see Appendix E
Ascot Finish - 4.1: 1976
Ascot Paddock - 4.1: undated, 1979
The Queen at Ascot - 3.1: Knoedler London Solo Exhibition 1976, 3.1: Heit Galleries Solo Exhibition, Phoenix 1976
Saratoga Harness, 1969, 1974 - 3.1: Saratoga Harness 1969, 1974
Seattle Slew - 2.1: 1977, 4.1: 1975
Secretariat, Secretariat at the Lead, 1974 - 2.1: 1990, 1992, 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95, 4.1: 1975, 1981, 1993 ov, VII: Pendants
Secretariat II - 4.1: 1990
Show Jumper - 4.1: undated 1970s, 1978
Sportsman's Park, Chicago - 3.1: Sportsman's Park Mural, Chicago 1976
Steeplechase, 1974 watercolor - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975-76
Stretch Stampede, 1975 - 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95
Study for Gericault Horse without Rider - 4.1: 1982
Tentam - 4.1: 1973
Thoroughbred Times - 4.1: 1993
T.O.B.A. - 2.1: 2000
Wayne Newton's State of the Art September Sale - 4.1: 1985
Hospital Relief Fund of the Caribbean - 4.1: 1984
Hotel des Artistes - 1.1: Residences - Hotel des Artistes
House Beautiful Magazine - 4.1: 1965
Houston Astrodome - 4.1: 1971
Houston International Film Festival - 3.1: Houston Film Fest 1990
Howard, Frank, Frank Howard, 1970s - 4.1: 1998
Howe, Gordie - 4.1: 1975
Gordie Howe, 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Hudson Valley Writers Center - 4.1: 1990
Hull, Bobby - 4.1: 1977
Bobby Hull - 3.1: TIME Magazine Cover Portraits Exhibition, National Portrait Gallery and St. Paul Art Center 1969, 4.1: 1968, 1986
Humane Society of New York - 4.1: 1994, 1995, 1996, 1998
Humphrey, President Hubert, Hubert Humphrey, date unknown - 2.1: 1994
Hunt, Lamar
Lamar Hunt, 1972 - 4.1: 1972
The Hunt for the Unicorn, late 1960s mural - see animals: unicorn
The Hustler - 4.1: 1985
Hutscnecker, Dr. Arnold A. - 4.1: 1981
I
I Am Third by Gale Sayers - 4.1: 1970, 1975
Ibis Art Productions - 4.1: 1988
Ice Palace, 1985 - see Saint Paul, Minnesota
Iceland - 4.1: 1972
Idle Boat - 4.1: 1950s
Iglesias, Julio
Julio Iglesias, 1984 - 2.1: 2001, 3.1: Julio Iglesias, 1984, 4.1: 1998, 2001
Illinois Art Education Association - 4.1: 1974
imitators - 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries
In the Pocket, 1988 - see football - Superbowl XXII
income - IID: Invoices Paid
India - 2.1: 1982
Indianapolis 500 - see auto racing
Indianapolis Museum of Art - 2.1: 1976, 4.1: 1977, see also exhibitions
Intelligent Doubles, by Skip Singleton - see tennis
Intelligent Tennis by Skip Singleton - see tennis
International Heart Foundation - see The Open Heart, 1982
International Management Group, Inc. - 2.1: 1977
International Poker, 2004 serigraph and earlier painting - see casinos
International Sephardic Education Foundation - 4.1: 1987
Introduction of the Champions of the Ring, 1964-65 (or Ringside Madison Square Garden) - see boxing
investing, investors - 3.1: L. Roy Papp, 1980, 3.1: Mustang Ranch Brothel 1989
Iona College - 1.1: Honorary Degrees ov., 2.2: Manufacturers Hanover, 3.1: Iona College
Trustee Awards Dinner Dances 1984-95, 4.1: 2000
Irish Fair - see Great Irish Fair
Iron Horse Steak House - 4.1: Undated
Isbin, Sharon - 2.1: 1996, 1997
Israel - 3.1: Peace Treaty, 1980
J
Jackson, Bo - 4.1: 1992
Jackson, Michael - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
Jackson, Phil - 4.1: 1994
Jackson, Reggie - 2.1: 1992, 2000, 2001, 4.1: 1978
Reggie Jackson, 1993 - 4.1: 1993
Jacobs, Jason, Accountant - 2.1: 1977, 1984
Jacobs, Jim
Jim Jacobs, 1970 - 2.1: 1992, 4.1: 1970, 1992
Jamaica - 4.2: Playboy 1971, see Appendix E
Japan - 2.1: 1986, 1987, 2.2: CBS Sports Correspondence, 3.1: Hawaii and Japan 1974, 3.1: Japan Trip 1977, 3.1: Tokyo Exhibition 1983, 3.1: Tokyo Exhibition 1988, 3.2. Winners, 1983, Correspondence, Harry N. Abrams, 4.1: 1984
jazz
Armstrong, Louis - 3.1: "Louis Armstrong: A Cultural Legacy" traveling exhibition 1995, 4.1: undated 1990s
Louis Armstrong, 1963 - 4.1: 1965
Louis Armstrong, 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Louis Armstrong, 1976 - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975 -2004, 3.1: Kool Jazz Festival 1976, 4.1: 1979
Satch, 1959 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989
Davis, Miles
Miles Davis, 1985 - 4.1: 1985
Ellington, Duke
Duke, 1978 - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004, 4.1: 1979, 1981
"Duke", 1998 - 3.1: UCLA 1998-present
Fitzgerald, Ella
Ella in Flight, 1983 - 3.1: Ella in Flight, 1983
Gillespie, Dizzy
Bird & Diz, 1973 - 4.1: 1973
Holiday, Billie
"Lady", 1979 - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004
Jazz Horns, 2004 painting and serigraph - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004, 4.1: 2004, 2005
Jazzmobile - 2.2: Jazzmobile 1980-84
Jazzmobile, 1975 silkscreen - 2.1: 1975, 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975-76
Kenton, Stan
Stan Kenton, 1976 - 2.1: 1975, 4.1: 1985
Kool Jazz Festival - 3.1: Kool Jazz Festival 1976, 4.1: 1981, 1982, 1985, V: 1980s
Newport Jazz Festival - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004
Newport Jazz, 2004 - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004
Newport Jazz Festival Poster, 1974 - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004
Orchestra - 4.1: 1964
Parker, Charlie - Bird & Diz, 1973 - 4.1: 1973, Charlie 'Bird' Parker - 3.1: Newport Jazz Festival 1975-2004
Playboy Jazz Festival, 1980 - 4.1: 1980
The Jeanie Johnston, 1998 - 4.1: 1999
Jenner, Bruce - see track and field
The Jennifer, 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Jeopardy! -2.1: 1998
Jimmy Fund - 3.1: Ted Williams and Jimmy Fund 1991
JoAnn Perse Gallery -2.2: JoAnn Perse Gallery 1984-98, 3.1: John Lennon Etching 1990
Jock Magazine - 4.1: 1970
jockeys - see horses: horse racing
Johnson, Cecile Ryden - 4.1: 1975
Johnson, Earvin "Magic" - Magic, 1988 - 2.1: 1992, 4.1: 1989 ov, Magic Johnson, 1991 - 2.1: 1996
Jones, Baird - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions, New York 1988-89, 4.1: 1987, 1988
Jones, Robert Trent - 4.1: 1995
Jones, Jr., Roy - see boxing
Jones, Tony - 1.1: Education and Teaching b., see AppendixA for correspondence
Jordan, Michael, Michael Jordan - 4.1: undated 1990s, 2000, Michael Jordan, serigraph - 2.1: 1991, 4.1: 1998
Joyner -Kersee, Jackie - see track and field
J.R. Fine Arts - 4.1: 1998
judo - 4.1: 1977, 1987
Juvenile Diabetes Foundation - 4.1: 1990, 1991, 1995
K
Kabl Citizen of the Day Award - 1.1: Awards
Kalinsky, George - 2.1: 1984, 1986, 1996, 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries, George Kalinsky with his Olympus, 1986 drawing - 4.1: 1986
Kaplan, Fred - 2.1: 1960s, 1970s
Kapp, Joe - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-1973, 4.1: 1970
Kaufman, Bart and Judy - 2.2: Bart Kaufman 1978-89, 4.1: 1970s
Kay, Leslie - 3.1: Folies Bergere, Tropicana, Las Vegas 1983
Kelly, Bob - 4.1: 1974
Kennedy Onassis, Jackie, Jackie, 1970 drawing - 4.1: 1970
Kennedy, Robert and Ethel - 3.1: Robert F. Kennedy Pro Celebrity Tennis Tournament 1972-79, 4.1: 1968, 1971, 1972 see also golf, tennis
Ethel Kennedy - 3.1: "Recent Graphics and Drawings," The Far Gallery Solo Exhibition 1971
R.F.K., 1968 watercolor - 4.1: 1968
Robert F. Kennedy, 1971 engraving - 3.1: "Recent Graphics and Drawings", The Far Gallery Solo Exhibition 1971, 4.1: 1972, 1974
Kennedy, Ted
Sen. Ted Kennedy, 1981 drawing on napkin - 4.1: 1981
Kenneth Behm Galleries - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1987, V: 1991
Kenton, Stan - see jazz
Kentucky Derby - see horse racing
Kerner, Otto - 4.1: 1960
Kershaw, Tom - 4.1: 1995
Key Club Bar, 1956 - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992
Kidd, Billy - 3.1: '21' Club, 1990 (photo)
Kilroy, Gene - 2.2: Gene Kilroy, 3.1: Golden Nugget Casino, Las Vegas 1988
King, Don - 3.1: Sportsman's Ball 1978, 4.1: 1975
King, Larry - 4.1: 1988 (radio), Larry King, 1996 - 3.1: Morton's of Chicago 1982-present
King, Mark - 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries
King's Palace, 1960 drawing - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992
Kitt, Eartha - 4.1: 1994
Knight, Bobby, Bobby Knight, 1979 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989, Knoedler & Co. - IID: Price Lists, 1.2: Knoedler & Co. and Hammer Galleries, see also Appendix B, Hammer Galleries - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman in Moscow" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries 1987, 3.1: Soft Paintings 1989, 3.1: "A Salute to Central Park" Exhibition 1989, 3.1: Universal Geneve Timepieces Promotion 1995, 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams, 1.2: Knoedler & Co. and Hammer Galleries, 4.1: 1972, 1976, 1985, 1989, see also exhibitions
Knoedler Publishing - 3.1: Knoedler London Exhibition 1976, 3.2 Publications, 1.2: Knoedler & Co and Hammer Galleries, 4.1: 1976, 1989
Kohl Galleries - 4.1: 1988
Kool Jazz Festival - see jazz
Koosman, Jerry, Jerry Koosman, 1976 - 4.1: 1977, 2001
Kopf, Chef Stefan - 4.1: 1986
Kozlova, Valentina - V: 1991
Kramer, Paul - 4.1: 1980
Kravtiz, Brenda - 1.1: Friars
Kupcinet, Irv "Kup" - see television, see also Appendix A
Kushner, Cedric - see Heavyweight Explosion
L
La Cuisine Francaise - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994 -1999, 3.1: The Culinary Arts 1998, 4.1: 1995, 1998, Le Grand Cuisine, 1977 - 2.1: 2000, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1997-2002, 4.1: 1977, 2001
La Nuit de Paris, 1988 - 4.1: 1988, 1989
Lacrosse - 4.1: 1977, 2005, see also McEneaney, Eamon
U.S.A. Lacrosse Team - 4.1: 1978
Ladies of the Hunt, 1959 charcoal - see horses
Lagerfeld, Karl - 4.1: 1992
Lake Tahoe - VC: 1983
LaLanne, Jack - 2.1: 1977, 3.2. Horses, 1979, Harry N. Abrams, Correspondence
Landau, Barry - 2.2: Barry Landau 1994-96
Landry, Tom - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-1973, Tom Landry, 1984 - 4.1: 1984 ov., 1989
Lanier Business Products, Inc. - see Stock Market, 1976
Largent, Steve - 4.1: 1994
Lark Creek Inn - 4.1: 1990
Larry Harper Company - 4.1: 1998
LaRussa, Tony - 2.1: 1993, Manager of the Year, 1992 - 4.1: 1993
Larson, Glen and Janet - 2.1: 1985, 1987
Lasorda, Tommy - 4.1: 1993
Las Vegas - see casinos, 1.1: Awards, 3.1: Las Vegas Centennial 2005
Las Vegas Celebrity Cookbook - 2.1: 1984
Latin Legends film - 4.1: Undated 1990s
Latin Recording Academy - see Appendix A
law suits - 2.2: Fried, Frank, Harris, Shriver & Jacobson Attorneys, 4.1: 1975, see also forgery, theft
against Felicie Schumsky, by LeRoy Neiman, 1976 - 1.2
against Robert Gold d/b/a Gallery Artists, 1976 - 2.2: Fried, Frank, Harris, Shriver & Jacobson Attorneys
against LeRoy Neiman and Knoedler, Inc. by Emerald Art Gallery, 1977 - 2.1: 1977
Lawrence Ross Galleries - 3.1: Lawrence Ross Galleries 1985-88
lawyers - 2.2: Fried, Frank, Harris, Shriver & Jacobson Attorneys
Lazar, Irving "Swifty" - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
Leahy, Pat - 4.1: 1992
Learning Annex - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1989
Lebow, Fred - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
lectures - 2.2: Royce Carlton Lecture Agents 1978-86, 4.1: 1989, see also Learning Annex
Leibowitz, Maury - 1.2: Knoedler & Co. and Hammer Galleries
Leifer, Neil - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 3.1: '21' Club, 1990 (photo), 4.1: 2003
Leija, James - 4.1: 1995
LeMieux, Mario, Mario LeMieux, 1989 - 2.2: DeBartolo Corporation and Associated Institutions 1989-91
Lendl, Ivan - see tennis
Lennon, John - 2.1: 1999, 2000, see also The Beatles, and Ono, Yoko
John Lennon, pre 1982 drawing - 4.1: 1982
John Lennon, 1990 etching - 2.2: JoAnn Perse Gallery 1984-98, 3.1: John Lennon Etching 1990, 4.1: 1990, 1992
Leonard, Sugar Ray - see boxing
LeRoy, Minnesota - 4.1: 1978 and ov, V: 1970s
LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994 - 3.1: Superbowl XXVIII 1994, 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994
LeRoy Neiman: Art and Lifestyle, 1974 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman Art and Lifestyle, 1974, Felicie, 1.2: Felicie, Inc. Advertising, 1.2: Lawsuit Against Felicie, Inc.
LeRoy Neiman Center for Print Studies, Columbia University - 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Center for Print Studies, Columbia University 1995-present
LeRoy Neiman Center for the Study of American Society and Culture, University of California at Los Angeles - 3.1: UCLA, 1998-present
LeRoy Neiman: Five Decades, 2003 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: Five Decades, 2003
LeRoy Neiman Museum of Art, St. Paul, Minnesota - 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Museum of Art, St. Paul, 1997, 4.1: 1997 (ov), 1998
LeRoy Neiman On Safari, 1996 - 1.2: Bowles Galleries 1997-present, 3.2. LeRoy Neiman On Safari, 1996
LeRoy, Warner - 2.1: 1998, 1999, V: 1991, see also Tavern on the Green
Let's Celebrate - 4.1: undated
Leukemia Society of America - 4.1: 1992
Levin, Meyer - 4.1: 1955-59
Lewis, Carl - see track and field
Lewis, Jerry Lee - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004, The Killer - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004
Lewis, Lennox - see boxing
Liberace - 4.1: 1988
Licensing Art and Design, by Cynthia Revelli - 2.1: 1995
Lido - 4.2: Playboy 1964, see Appendix E
Lifeline Inc. (fitness equipment) - 2.2: Bobby Hinds 1990-2000
Lifestyle Magazine - 4.1: Undated 1980s
Lilly, Bob, Bob Lilly, 1972 - 4.1: 1972
Limbaugh, Rush - 4.1: 1991
Limoges enamels - 2.1: 1988
Lincoln, Abraham, Abraham Lincoln, 1968 - 2.1: 1988, 1989, 4.1: 1968, 1981, 1987
Lindberg, Elayne - 3.1: Stadium Tennis Billboard, 1981 (photo)
Lipofsky, Mary and Steve - 2.1: 1996, 4.1: 1995
Liston, Sonny - see boxing
Little, Floyd - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-73, 4.1: 1973 ov
Floyd Little - 4.1: 1972
The Littlest Clown - 4.1: undated
Liverpool, England - 4.1: 1960 ov
Lollobrigida, Gina - 4.1: 1981
Loma Linda University - 2.1: 1983
Lombardi, Vince, Vince, 1981 - 2.1: 2001, 4.1: 1985
Lomonaco, Chef Michael - 2.1: 1996, 4.1: 1999
London, England - 3.1: O'Hana Gallery Solo Exhibition, London 1962, 3.1: Knoedler London Exhibition 1976, 4.1: 1960 ov, 1961, 1962, 1966, see also Liverpool
The Lone Ranger, 1977 - 2.1: 1988, 3.1: The Lone Ranger, 1977
Long, Captain Elgen, The Adventurer, between 1971 and 1977 - 2.2: Gallery Mack 1975 -87, 4.1: 1982
Lonsdale International Sporting Club - 1.1: Awards
Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art (LAICA) - 3.1: Neiman/Warhol Exhibition at LAICA 1981-82
Louganis, Greg - see swimming and diving
Louis, Allyson - see Allyson Louis Gallery
Louis, Joe - see boxing
Lowery, Nick
Nick Lowery, 1992 - 4.1: 1992, 1997
Lubel, William - 2.1: 1973
Lynch, David - 3.1: "Cig Art" Benefit Exhibitions 1996-2000
M
Maccioni, Sirio - 4.1: 2004
Mack, Barbara - see Gallery Mack
Madison Square Garden - 2.1: 1981, 4.1: 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971, 1987, 1992, 1994, 1999, 4.2: Playboy 1963, see Appendix E